[
    {
        "question": "♖🍔  *_~`ويليام`~_*  👌😺",
        "response": "ويليام"
    },
    {
        "question": "♕☝  *_~`نامي`~_*  ♢🍭",
        "response": "نامي"
    },
    {
        "question": "🍩🎉  *_~`ايرين`~_*  ♙✌",
        "response": "ايرين"
    },
    {
        "question": "♣👑  *_~`استا`~_*  ☯🍩",
        "response": "استا"
    },
    {
        "question": "♝💚  *_~`همتارو`~_*  💘💥",
        "response": "همتارو"
    },
    {
        "question": "🐟💲  *_~`الويفيا`~_*  🐧🎯",
        "response": "الويفيا"
    },
    {
        "question": "☆🎯  *_~`نويل`~_*  ♤♚",
        "response": "نويل"
    },
    {
        "question": "🎅🐸  *_~`رايلي`~_*  ♟👍",
        "response": "رايلي"
    },
    {
        "question": "✋♬  *_~`ال`~_*  ൠ✋",
        "response": "ال"
    },
    {
        "question": "🐍💀  *_~`لاو`~_*  ☮♔",
        "response": "لاو"
    },
    {
        "question": "💗🍫  *_~`مادارا`~_*  🐟🐧",
        "response": "مادارا"
    },
    {
        "question": "▀▄▀▄▀▄ *_~`يوريتشي`~_* ▄▀▄▀▄▀",
        "response": "يوريتشي"
    },
    {
        "question": "♝🎃  *_~`ايتاتشي`~_*  ♞✊",
        "response": "ايتاتشي"
    },
    {
        "question": "💣👌  *_~`توبي`~_*  ☜🐠",
        "response": "توبي"
    },
    {
        "question": "🎁🏆  *_~`نوبارا`~_*  💔🍟",
        "response": "نوبارا"
    },
    {
        "question": "🐔  🎀  *_~`ليفاي`~_*  🎀  🐔",
        "response": "ليفاي"
    },
    {
        "question": "☢⛵  *_~`هاشيراما`~_*  ♝😎",
        "response": "هاشيراما"
    },
    {
        "question": "🐒💙  *_~`بوروتو`~_*  😳♕",
        "response": "بوروتو"
    },
    {
        "question": "💜🎈  *_~`يوسوب`~_*  💗🔥",
        "response": "يوسوب"
    },
    {
        "question": "🍰  🎀  *_~`ريم`~_*  🎀  🍰",
        "response": "ريم"
    },
    {
        "question": "☠👤  *_~`اوتشيها شيسوي`~_*  ♥♪",
        "response": "اوتشيها شيسوي"
    },
    {
        "question": "✋🔥  *_~`كيد`~_*  🎈✋",
        "response": "كيد"
    },
    {
        "question": " ▂ ▄ ▅ ▆ ▇ █  *_~`ميكاسا`~_*  █ ▇ ▆ ▅ ▄ ▂",
        "response": "ميكاسا"
    },
    {
        "question": "(っ◔◡◔)っ ♥ *_~`دانزو`~_* ♥",
        "response": "دانزو"
    },
    {
        "question": "☮💣  *_~`وينغ`~_*  ൠ😎",
        "response": "وينغ"
    },
    {
        "question": "🎉😺  *_~`تينشيهان`~_*  🐼🐊",
        "response": "تينشيهان"
    },
    {
        "question": "*_~`بيكوهان`~_*",
        "response": "بيكوهان"
    },
    {
        "question": "💥👑  *_~`كازيكاجي`~_*  👮💣",
        "response": "كازيكاجي"
    },
    {
        "question": "👤♤  *_~`جيرايا`~_*  👺♦",
        "response": "جيرايا"
    },
    {
        "question": "🐉☯  *_~`كازيكاجي`~_*  🐊♕",
        "response": "كازيكاجي"
    },
    {
        "question": "♘👤  *_~`كوكومي`~_*  🐺🎃",
        "response": "كوكومي"
    },
    {
        "question": "🔥👻  *_~`غيو`~_*  ♡💚",
        "response": "غيو"
    },
    {
        "question": "🐟♥  *_~`تشيو`~_*  🐟☯",
        "response": "تشيو"
    },
    {
        "question": "🔥♝  *_~`ساسوري`~_*  👣👹",
        "response": "ساسوري"
    },
    {
        "question": "✷  🎀  *_~`نيزوكو`~_*  🎀  ✷",
        "response": "نيزوكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "🌷🐉  *_~`ميدوريا`~_*  🐸👽",
        "response": "ميدوريا"
    },
    {
        "question": "♣✌  *_~`نيجي`~_*  🐺💎",
        "response": "نيجي"
    },
    {
        "question": "🐺🐤  *_~`استا`~_*  🐯🐨",
        "response": "استا"
    },
    {
        "question": "👑🏆  *_~`ليزا`~_*  ♢🍧",
        "response": "ليزا"
    },
    {
        "question": "👑🎯  *_~`كاغويا`~_*  💀🐣",
        "response": "كاغويا"
    },
    {
        "question": "🐧  🎀  *_~`هينا`~_*  🎀  🐧",
        "response": "هينا"
    },
    {
        "question": "🐓  🎀  *_~`الوكا`~_*  🎀  🐓",
        "response": "الوكا"
    },
    {
        "question": "ıllıllı   🎀  *_~`هيناتا`~_*  🎀   ıllıllı",
        "response": "هيناتا"
    },
    {
        "question": "🐤🍬  *_~`زينتسو`~_*  💢🍪",
        "response": "زينتسو"
    },
    {
        "question": "👻🍓  *_~`رينغوكو`~_*  🐧🔥",
        "response": "رينغوكو"
    },
    {
        "question": "💝💲  *_~`ليفاي`~_*  ☆💗",
        "response": "ليفاي"
    },
    {
        "question": "💢☟  *_~`كورتا`~_*  🎈💣",
        "response": "كورتا"
    },
    {
        "question": "😈🎈  *_~`هيسوكا`~_*  💙🎃",
        "response": "هيسوكا"
    },
    {
       "question": "💎♘  *_~`انوس`~_*  😝👑",
        "response": "انوس"
    },
    {
       "question": "☟🎈  *_~`بياكوغان`~_*  💎♧",
        "response": "بياكوغان"
    },
    {
       "question": "【｡_｡】 *_~`شوكو`~_* 【｡_｡】",
        "response": "شوكو"
    },
    {
       "question": "🐍🐧  *_~`ديكو`~_*  🎄✊",
        "response": "ديكو"
    },
    {
       "question": "░▒▓█ *_~`يامي`~_* █▓▒░",
        "response": "يامي"
    },
    {
       "question": "🏆👍  *_~`فانجانس`~_*  🍮🎅",
        "response": "فانجانس"
    },
    {
       "question": "☮🐤  *_~`يوليوس`~_*  🐜♜",
        "response": "يوليوس"
    },
    {
       "question": "👊✊  *_~`تسوموغو`~_*  🐣🐨",
        "response": "تسوموغو"
    },
    {
       "question": "👻💛  *_~`نانامي`~_*  🎃💛",
        "response": "نانامي"
    },
    {
       "question": "🐠🐍  *_~`ايزن`~_*  ♗♚",
        "response": "ايزن"   
    },
    {
       "question": "♔💎  *_~`زاراكي`~_*  ✌☆",
        "response": "زاراكي"
    },
    {
       "question": "🐻💜  *_~`اوراهارا`~_*  ☹🐺",
        "response": "اوراهارا"
    },
    {
       "question": "🍩🍪  *_~`اينوي`~_*  ☹👹",
        "response": "اينوي"
    },
    {
       "question": "👽🐉  *_~`غوهان`~_*  🐲♝",
        "response": "غوهان"
    },
    {
       "question": "🐲♕  *_~`كيريلين`~_*  😲🐊",
        "response": "كيريلين"
    },
    {
       "question": "*•.¸♡ *_~`هيناتسورو`~_* ♡¸.•*",
        "response": "هيناتسورو"
    },
    {
       "question": "-漫~*'¨¯¨'*·舞~ *_~`ريتشيل`~_* ~舞*'¨¯¨'*·~漫-",
       "response": "ريتشيل"
}
]
